<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RS:Study</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Calendar</string>
    <string name="title_statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="item2">Item2</string>
    <string name="setting">Item3</string>
    <string name="dark">Item4</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key" />
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>


    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="account_header">Account</string>
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>
    <string name="theme_header">Theme</string>

    <!-- Account Preferences -->
    <string name="Name_title">Name Surname</string>
    <string name="Nickname_title">Name Surname</string>
    <string name="Email_title">E-mail</string>
    <string name="Educational_title">Educational institution</string>

    <!-- Theme preferences -->
    <string name="Application_theme_change">Application theme change</string>
    <string name="Auto_theme_on">Auto
    </string>
    <string name="Auto_theme_off">Manual</string>
    <string name="Selection_title">Select</string>
    <string name="about_text">In nowadays rapidly developing world where multitasking is essential for productive activities, our hard-working team would like to present you with the ultimate solution to track your educational progress most effectively. This planner app is honored to keep an eye on your courses, lessons and deadlines and reminding you periodically. Our goal is to relieve stress in the educational life of students around the world.</string>
    <string name="rights">© 2020, REDISS team, All rights reserved</string>
    <string name="email">rsstydyrediss@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="policydata">We do not track you, as well as we do not profile you. We value your privacy ;)</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="IntroduceText">Welcome to the RS:Study guide! Here we will introduce you to the basic functions of the application and how to use them.</string>
    <string name="ManualText1">Firstly, right after entering the application, the screen in front of your eyes is the main menu. What we recommend you do first is customize your profile section by clicking the gear button in the top right corner.</string>
    <string name="ManualText2">Your new profile will be accessible from the main menu by clicking the avatar button in the upper left corner. You can upload your profile picture on the same screen by clicking the avatar in the circle to make your account even more unique!</string>
    <string name="ManualText3">After your profile is customized, we would like to show you how to add courses and lessons into them. First press the plus button in the middle of the main screen with the course sign, then give your course a name and number of lessons per week. Then for each lesson, you can add its date, duration and whether it should be repeated or not. After you add them all to the course, you can see the upcoming lesson on the main screen.</string>
    <string name="ManualText4">In case you need to add more lessons, instead of creating a new course, you can simply add more to the existing ones. To do this, press the plus button with the lesson sign in the center of the main screen and select the course to which you want to add additional lessons.</string>
</resources>